edirectory.com 2017-07-08

# 

Arca Solutions, Inc., developers of eDirectory software, (“Arca”, “we”, “our”, or “us”) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of personal information we receive via our Service (as defined in the Terms of Service below) from users of our Service. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time. We will notify you of any material changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Website. Your use of the Service following any such notice will signify and constitute your assent to and acceptance of such revised Privacy Policy. 

## 1\. Information Collection and Use

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means information that can be used to uniquely identify you, such as your name, telephone number, address, and e-mail address. 

**Personal Information We Collect**

When you interact with us, we may ask you to supply us with Personal Information. For example, we may collect Personal Information when you:

  1. Use our Service, including our Website, or use/download any of our Apps;
  2. Request quotes, support, information, or access to our information products and services;
  3. Download Content, software or a software update;
  4. Subscribe to newsletters, promotional emails, alerts, updates or other materials; or
  5. Register for webinars or other content offers
  6. Contact us.

**Our Use of Your Personal Information**

We mainly use your Personal Information, either alone or in combination with other information, so that we can provide, enhance and personalize our Service and our marketing efforts.

The following are examples of a variety of ways that we may use your Personal Information. We may use your Personal Information:

  1. To provide you with the best customer experience possible;
  2. To provide the products and services you purchase, respond to your questions, and carry out the transactions you have requested;
  3. To communicate with you regarding updates, offers, orders, and promotions;
  4. To help us develop, customize, deliver, support and improve our services, products, content, and advertising;
  5. To help authenticate any account you create with us;
  6. To administer promotions;
  7. To serve advertisements on our Website;
  8. To protect the rights or property of Arca or our users, and prevent fraud and other prohibited or illegal activities;
  9. To protect the security of our products, services, and business;
  10. For our internal purposes (such as auditing, data analysis, and research to improve our products, services, and communications); and
  11. Otherwise, as disclosed to you at the point of collection.

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive communications from us, please follow any unsubscribe instructions that may be provided in our communications to you, or update your user preferences via e-mail subscription management tools on our Website. Please note that we may use your Personal Information to contact you with important notifications, such as notices with respect to purchases, safety, or changes to our terms, conditions, and policies; you may not opt out of these notifications.

**Blogs, Social Media and other Public Forums**

We may offer blogs, social media profiles, message boards, bulletin boards or similar public forums where you and other users of our Service can post content or otherwise communicate. The protections described in this Privacy Policy do not apply when you provide information (including personally identifiable information about any person) in connection with your use of these public forums. We may use your name to identify you with a posting in a public forum. Any information you share in a public forum is public information and may be seen or collected by other persons, including third parties that do not adhere to the standards set forth in this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for events arising from the distribution of any information you choose to publicly post or share through our online services.

**Collection and Use of Non-Identifying Information**

We may collect, use, transfer, and disclose information in a form that does not personally identify you (“Non-Identifying Information”) for any purpose. Non-Identifying Information can include certain Personal Information that has been de-identified; that is, information that has been rendered anonymous. We and/or our third party service providers obtain Non-Identifying Information about you from information that you provide us, either separately or together with your Personal Information. We and/or our third party service providers also automatically collect certain Non-Identifying Information from you when you access our Service.

Certain Non-Identifying Information about you would be considered a part of your Personal Information if it were combined with other identifiers in a way that enables you to be identified. But the same pieces of information are considered Non-Identifying Information when they are taken alone or combined only with other Non-Identifying information. We may combine your Personal Information with Non-Identifying Information and aggregate it with information collected from other users or sources to attempt to provide you with a better experience, to improve the quality and value of our products and services, and to analyze and understand how our products and services are used. We may also use the combined information without aggregating it to serve you specifically.

**Non-Identifying Information We Automatically Collect**

When you access the Service via a web browser, App, or other client, we and our third-party service providers may use a variety of technologies, now and hereafter devised, that automatically record certain usage information. This information may include your Internet Protocol address (and other unique identifiers for the particular device you use to access the Internet), browser type, your web or application request, your interaction with our Service, the webpage or services feature you were using before you came to our Service, pages of our Website that you visit, information you search for via our Service, access times and dates, and other similar information. We use this information for a variety of purposes, including analyzing and enhancing our products and services, and to help personalize our Service for you. We do not treat this information as Personal Information (except to the extent required by local law), although if we combine it with the Personal Information you provide, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information. We and our third-party service providers may automatically collect Non-Identifying Information using various methods, including, without limitation, the following methods.

  * **Cookies.** A cookie is a small data file transferred to your computer (or other device) when it is used to access our Service. Cookies may be used for many purposes, including to enable certain features of our Service, to better understand how you interact with our Service and to monitor aggregate usage by visitors and online traffic routing. You may be able to instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the online services you visit. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of our Service or all functionality of our Service.
  * **Click-Through URLs.** In some of our e-mail communications, we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on our websites. When users click one of these URLs, they pass through a separate web server before arriving at the destination page on our Website. We may track this click-through data to help us determine interest in particular topics and measure the effectiveness of our customer communications. If you prefer not to be tracked in this way, you should not click text or graphic links in the email messages.

**App Identifiers.** Certain of our Apps may include a unique application number that is not associated with you. This number may be sent to us when you install or uninstall Apps or when such Apps periodically contact our servers (for example, to request automatic software updates).

**Third Party Advertising Technology**

Our Service may use third parties such as network advertisers to serve advertisements and may use traffic measurement services to analyze traffic. Third-party ad serving enables advertisements to be targeted to you for products and services in which you might be interested.

Third party ad network providers, the advertisers, the sponsors and/or traffic measurement services may themselves set and access their own cookies and other technologies on your personal computer and/or device and track certain behavioral information regarding users of your personal computer and/or mobile device. These third party cookies and other technologies are set to, among other things: (a) help deliver advertisements to you that you might be interested in; (b) prevent you from seeing the same advertisements too many times; and (c) understand the usefulness to you of the advertisements that have been delivered to you. Note that any images (or any other parts of a web page) served by third parties in association with third party cookies may serve as web beacons, which enable third parties to carry out the previously described activities. Third party cookies, web beacons, and other third party technologies are governed by each third party's specific privacy policy, not this one.

## 2\. Information Sharing and Disclosure

Except as described in this Privacy Policy, we will not share your Personal Information with other companies or individuals outside of Arca unless we have received your consent. Non-Identifying Information may be provided to third parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Our Service Providers and Other Third Parties**

We may engage third party companies and individuals to perform services on our behalf (e.g., without limitation, software maintenance services, advertising serving technologies, e-mail service providers, delivery services, database management, web analytics and other services). These third parties may have access to your Personal Information. If they do, this access is provided so that they may perform these tasks on our behalf and they are not authorized by us to otherwise use or disclose your Personal Information, except to the extent required by law. In addition, if you choose to participate in certain of our programs or to receive certain content we make available (e.g., webinar programs), we may share your Personal Information with participating sponsors, content providers, and related vendors in connection with such programs and content.

**Compliance with Laws, Legal Process and Authorities**

We cooperate with government and law enforcement officials and private parties to enforce and comply with the law. We will disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we, in our sole discretion, believe necessary or appropriate to respond to claims and legal process (including but not limited to subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of us or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable.

**Data Transfer**

Arca processes personal information on our servers. Your Personal Information may be transferred to, and used, in locations outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the privacy laws may not be as protective as those in your jurisdiction. You hereby consent to such transfer and use in all respects.

**Business Transfers**

Circumstances may arise where, whether for strategic or other business reasons, we may sell, transfer or otherwise disclose some or all of our assets, including your Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets or in the event of bankruptcy. It’s Arca’s practice to seek appropriate protection for information in these types of transactions.

### 3\. General

**Changing or Deleting Your Information**

Arca has implemented technology, management processes and policies to help maintain data accuracy. Arca makes good faith efforts to provide individuals with reasonable access to Personal Information that they have provided to Arca and the reasonable ability to review and correct it or ask for deletion, as applicable, if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. To view and change Personal Information that you have directly provided to our Service, you can follow the instructions on the Website, or contact Arca in writing at support@edirectory.com. Please note we may retain server/backup copies of all such data, and that we may decline to process change or deletion requests that we deem to be unreasonable, or require disproportionate technical effort, or jeopardize the privacy of others.

**Security**

We employ appropriate security measures to protect your Personal Information from unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure, or destruction. These security measures include administrative, technical, and physical precautions to safeguard your Personal Information against loss, theft, and misuse. Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your Personal Information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and are not responsible for the theft, destruction or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information.

**Third Party Products and Service**

Our Service contains links to, or content from, third party websites and other products and services. The fact that we link to a website or display an advertisement or other third party content is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with any of those third parties, nor is it an endorsement of their privacy or information security policies or practices.

We do not exercise control over third party websites, products or services. These other products and services may place their own cookies or other files on your computer or other device, collect data or solicit personal information from you. Other persons and entities follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the information you submit to them or they collect from you. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.

**Our Policy Toward Children**

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 13 via our Service, and do not target our Service to children under 13. We encourage parents and guardians to take an active role in their children’s online activities and interests.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We will occasionally update this Privacy Policy. If we make changes, we will revise this Privacy Policy to reflect such changes and revise the effective date included at the end of this policy.

**Contacting Us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact Arca directly at support@edirectory.com.

Latest update: April 09 2017
